bostinno.com 2012-12-05

# Streetwise Media | Privacy Policy

**STREETWISE MEDIA, INC. PRIVACY POLICY**

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE STREETWISE TERMS OF SERVICE BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE OR ANY STREETWISE FORUM**

This Privacy Policy Statement ("Privacy Policy") is applicable to the Streetwise Media, Inc. ("Streetwise") Websites located at [http://streetwise-media.com](http://streetwise-media.com/), [http://bostinno.com](http://bostinno.com/), [http://inthecapital.com](http://inthecapital.com/), [http://intheempire.com](http://intheempire.com/) (the "Website" or “Websites”), and all services provided thereon ("Services"), including all Streetwise Channels, Comments, Community Features, Blogs, Forums ( as defined in the Terms of Service ). This Privacy Policy does not cover any interaction you may have with Streetwise by telephone, postal mail, or other offline communications.

**Notice**

Streetwise respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information that you provide in connection with your use of the Websites. This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you notice of Streetwise’s information practices, including the types of information gathered, how the information is used and safeguarded, and how you may control the maintenance and sharing of your information.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

You can visit the Streetwise Websites any time without providing any information about yourself. However, in order to use certain portions of the Services (e.g., to post articles, comment(s), or use other Community Features as described in the Streetwise Media, Inc. [Terms of Service](http://streetwise-media.com/corporate/termsofservice.html) **** (located at [http://streetwise-media.com/corporate/termsofservice.html](http://streetwise-media.com/corporate/termsofservice.html)), you may be required to register and create an “ **Account** ” as defined in the above mentioned [Terms of Service](http://streetwise-media.com/corporate/termsofservice.html).

There is no cost to create an Account, however, there may be a cost to update your company, business, or organizations Account to access or use premium Community Features. In either case, you will be asked to choose a user name, password, and display name, and to provide certain personally identifiable information, such as your real name and email address, age, address, and telephone numbers. As part of your Streetwise public profile, which may include your real name, you will be asked to provide additional personally identifiable information (PII) which may including your company, occupation, and bio; as well as other public profile links or references or PII including Twitter handle or link, Google+, LinkedIn, Facebook, or similar social services, as well as a RSS Feed of your Streetwise Community Feature activities.  Streetwise may publicly display this information in your public profile as well as part of your Community Feature activities, which include but are not limited to posts, comments, message boards, or chat rooms. If you do provide Streetwise with personally identifiable information, we will take all reasonable and appropriate steps to protect this information. We also urge you to keep your password confidential and refrain from sharing it with others. Streetwise will not disclose, share, sell or rent personally identifiable information to any third party without your prior consent.

Other than registration information, you may be asked to provide certain personal information in order to use or participate in certain promotions such as giveaways, sweepstakes, contests, surveys, newsletters, etc. ("Special Promotions"). In these instances, the Website will contain information regarding the intended use of the requested information.

Streetwise may also use technology, such as cookies (as described below), transparent gifs, web beacons, frames, server log analysis and other technologies as they are developed, to enhance your experience on Streetwise. 

**Special Notice Regarding Children Under 13 Years of Age**

Streetwise respects the privacy of children of all ages. Streetwise particularly recognizes the sensitivity of personal information concerning children under the age of 13 and therefore provides this special notice to parents and guardians regarding the collection and use of information collected from children in this age group.

The Streetwise Websites are not directed towards young children. Streetwise is intent on complying with applicable laws and regulations regarding children, including the United States ' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Specifically, Streetwise will not knowingly collect and maintain any personally identifiable information from children under 13. _If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personal information about yourself (such as your name, your e-mail address or your phone number). _Parents are hereby put on notice that as a result of the foregoing, Streetwise does not provide a mechanism to obtain parental consent.

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her personal information, Streetwise will make reasonable efforts to delete the information from its database, at your request. To request the deletion of your child's information, please send an email to [businessaffairs@streetwise-media.com](mailto:businessaffairs@streetwise-media.com) **** and be sure to include in your message the same user name and password that your child submitted.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

As part of the registration process to create a Streetwise Personal Account or to participate in Special Promotions, you may be asked to provide certain information that does not personally identify you. For example, you may be asked to provide information concerning your television viewing habits, music or other entertainment preferences, purchasing habits, and the like. Streetwise requests this information in order to enhance your online experience by understanding you better and to also make you aware of new services, programs or offers which may be of interest to you.

In general, you can browse Streetwise while remaining anonymous. However, in many cases, if you wish to interact on the Websites, Streetwise will collect certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of the Services. For example, Streetwise might collect information concerning the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, your "click path" through the Streetwise Websites, the Website or advertisement from which you linked to the Streetwise Website, and/or the Website that you go to when leaving the Streetwise Website. In order to do this, Streetwise may use several technologies and perform system checks when a user visits the Website. Examples of such technologies are cookies (as described below), transparent gifs, beacons, frames, server log analysis, and other technologies as they are developed. All technologies implemented on the Website are used to enhance the user experience.

Streetwise uses pixels, beacons, or transparent GIF files, to help manage its advertising campaigns. These files enable Streetwise to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our websites. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser or provider. With both cookies and transparent GIF files, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about how to opt out of these technologies, visit the [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out.

Streetwise allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn or more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising for some companies, you can visit the [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out.

As noted above, in general, Streetwise uses information to improve and enhance the Website, Services, and Community Features as well as to manage advertising, which supports our services, within applications, Community Features, on the Website, webpages, displayed on your computer, mobile devices, and/or tablets. However, from time to time, Streetwise may share this information with other entities in an aggregate, non-personally identifiable form to show general demographic and preference information among users of the Streetwise Websites.

**Online Store** ****

The Website may contain an online store from which you can purchase certain products and premium Community Features, including but not limited to advertising, job postings and premium channels. Stripe, located at [http://www.stripe.com](http://www.stripe.com/) handles all payment transactions for Streetwise. Streetwise does not store anything you input on a payment page. Specifically, we do not store the following PII information related to a payment transaction and asked for on the payment page, including but not limited to: your name, your address, your credit card number, your credit card expiration date, your credit card code on the back of the card. 

Streetwise encrypts the information (via SSL) that a user has inputted on a payment page and sends it to Stripe for processing- Stripe handles everything else. The user's credit card statement will show a purchase from Streetwise Media. Streetwise Media is PCI compliant, but does not have a merchant account and is not a payment gateway.

Streetwise may keep records of your transactions with us in order to communicate with you about products purchased, related customer support, and to send you information about other products or services we believe may be of interest to you.

**Cookies, Pixels, and Other Similar Technologies**

Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your computer, mobile phone or other device.  Pixels, transparent gifs or clear gifts, and web beacons are small blocks of code on webpages that do things like allow another server to measure viewing of a webpage and often are used in connection with cookies. The Streetwise Websites use technologies like cookies, pixels, and local storage, like on your browser or device, which is similar to a cookie but holds more information, to provide and understand a range of products and services. Streetwise uses these technologies to do things like:

· Make the Streetwise Websites easier or faster to use; 

· Facilitate your signing in to use the Website and its Community Features or Services;

· Enable Website, Community Features, and Services and to store information about you (including on your device or in your browser cache) and your use of the Streetwise Websites;

· Match your interests and preferences;

· Deliver, understand and improve advertising;

· Monitor and understand the use of our products, services, and Community Features;

· And to protect you, others and Streetwise.

Most Internet browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please note, however, that if you block cookies, many portions of the Website will not function properly. You should refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about how to manage cookies.

**Use of Information Collected**

Except as specifically outlined in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties without your permission. We may disclose aggregated information, such as demographic information, and certain statistical analysis to third parties, including advertisers and other business partners. This aggregated information will include any personal information. We may, however, share your personal information with our owners and other affiliated companies and their parents, subsidiaries, or affiliated companies, in order to provide portions of the Website and/or Services (e.g., to provide fulfillment for prizes won in a Streetwise sweepstakes or contest), or to provide other support for a Streetwise promotion. Please refer to the individual privacy policies of our affiliates for details concerning how they handle your personal and non-personal information.

Streetwise will not disclose your personal information to non-affiliated third parties, unless we have previously informed you of the disclosure, have been given your consent to disclose, or we are required by law to disclose. In the case of Special Promotions, the name of any third parties involved in the promotion will be disclosed, and when applicable, you may be given the option of providing your information to them. We reserve the right to disclose non-personal information in any way we deem appropriate.

Streetwise uses third party vendors to provide portions of the Website and its Services. By using the Services, you are deemed to consent to the use of these vendors. These vendors are contractually restricted to using personal information for the sole purpose of providing the Services and are strictly prohibited from sharing, selling, or otherwise distributing any personal data of our customers.

As stated in the Terms of Service, you will be deemed to have consented to the transfer and/or disclosure to a subsequent owner of this Website, of any personal information submitted by you and contained in the Streetwise database if Streetwise assigns all of its rights and obligations regarding the use of your personal information at the time of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of STREETWISE's assets.

Third-party advertisers may deliver specific advertisements to you on the Website. Such advertisers may collect non-personal information about your visits to the Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may also aggregate your non-personal information for use in targeted advertising, marketing research and other similar purposes. These companies may also place their own cookies on your computer. For a list of these commercial and advertising agencies and their privacy policies, as well as more information about your option not to accept cookies or clear gifs placed by these companies, please the [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). You can also visit each third-party advertiser's applicable website directly in order to opt-out from their use of this information.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

If you give Streetwise sensitive information (e.g., credit card numbers), Streetwise will take all commercially reasonable steps to protect such information by establishing a secure connection with your Web browser. Streetwise employs a security technology known as a secure-socket-layer ("SSL") to protect the transmission of payment information to the Website. Unless otherwise specified herein or on the Website, credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing or any other purposes.

While Streetwise takes precautions against possible breaches in its databases, no Website or internet transmission or connection is completely secure. Consequently, Streetwise cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur.

Streetwise urges you to keep your personal information safe by memorizing your password or keeping it in a safe place, separate from your account information, as sharing your password with others may lead to unauthorized access to your information.

**Postings to Streetwise Websites**

All comments or postings, whether in a chat room, on message boards, comment walls, channels, or other method of communication within the Website or Community Features will generally be available to, and freely accessible by, other users of the Streetwise Websites as well as the Internet general public. Therefore, users should not expect that any information they post will be kept private or confidential and are encouraged to exercise discretion when using the Streetwise Community Features. Additionally, your profile display name and or real name will always be included in conjunction with your postings in the Streetwise Community Features. Streetwise is not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through the Community Features.

**Hyperlinks To and From Other Websites**

The Website may contain links to, or advertisements concerning, other websites. Other websites may also reference, advertise, or link to Streetwise. Streetwise is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites and expressly disclaims all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other websites and advertisements. You should check the applicable privacy policy of any website you may click through to.

**Consent to Processing in the United States**

By providing any personal information to the Website, all users, including, without limitation, users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States of America.

**Maintaining and Updating Your Account Information**

As part of your use of the Services, you are responsible for maintaining and updating, as applicable, your Registration Information and Profile with current and complete information. You may edit and delete portions of your Streetwise Account information or delete the Account entirely. To do this, visit the Streetwise Website after signing in to your account, and click on "Edit Your Profile **"** to make changes or deletions. You can also write to us at:

Streetwise Media, Inc.   
Attn: Business Affairs  
Faneuil Hall, 1 South Market Building, 3rd Floor  
Boston, MA 02109

After receiving any requested changes to your information, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that all of your person information stored in databases we actively use to operate the Website will be updated, corrected, changes or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable. However, we reserve the right to retain in our archival files any information we remove from or change in our active website databases. We may retain such information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Service. In addition, it may not be technologically possible to remove every record of the information you have previously provided us, as a copy may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate.

If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13, and you have discovered that your child created an account and would like to have it deleted, please e-mail us at [businessaffairs@streetwise-media.com](mailto:businessaffairs@streetwise-media.com) with your child's member name and password.

**Contact Us Regarding Privacy**

Streetwise is dedicated to protecting your personal information and welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. You may e-mail us at the following address: [ businessaffairs@streetwise-media.com](mailto:%20businessaffairs@streetwise-media.com)

**Notification of Changes**

Streetwise reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying registered guests via email of the existence of a new Privacy Policy or by posting it on the Websites. Any changes to the Privacy Policy shall be effective when posted.

Last Updated Date: January 1, 2012
